A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative Files, 1956-2005; 1 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
  - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, 1964-2005; 2 (Reel 1, Frame 427)
    - Other Committees (Reel 12, Frame 672)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 2005 June 2 (Reel 13, Frame 1)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 2005 August 26 (Reel 13, Frame 29)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 2005 September 22 (Reel 13, Frame 69)
      - Finance Committee, Meeting, 2005 November 18 (Reel 13, Frame 108)
      - Policy Development, 1974-1984 (Reel 13, Frame 125)
      - Policy Development, 1977 (Reel 13, Frame 228)
      - Policy Retreat, 1984 June (Reel 13, Frame 239)
      - Policy Retreat, 1985 May 31-June 2 (Reel 13, Frame 280)
      - Policy Meeting, 1985 September 7 (Reel 13, Frame 329)
      - Policy Meeting, 1986 May 31 (Reel 13, Frame 344)
      - Policy Review Meeting, 1989 May 26-28 1989 June 7 (Reel 13, Frame 387)
      - Policy Meeting, 1990 August (Reel 13, Frame 401)
      - Policy Meeting, 1991 September (Reel 13, Frame 449)
      - Policy Meeting, 1992 September (Reel 13, Frame 487)
      - Policy Meeting, 1993 September (Reel 13, Frame 534)
      - Policy Meeting, 1995 September (Reel 13, Frame 579)
      - Program Area, Long-Range Outcomes and Strategic Objectives, 1989 June (Reel 13, Frame 612)
    - Reports (Reel 13, Frame 626)
      - Arkansas Education-Past, Present and Future, undated (Reel 13, Frame 627)
      - Blueprint for a Resource Information Center in Arkansas, Donella H. Meadows and Dennis L. Meadows, 1983 April 12 (Reel 13, Frame 659)
      - Developing Rural Arkansas, Thomas C. McRae, undated (Reel 13, Frame 689)
      - Economic Development, undated (Reel 13, Frame 695)
      - Guidelines for Grant Applications, 1993-1996 (Reel 13, Frame 739)
      - Healthcare in Arkansas, Paying Too Much for the Wrong Thing, 1979-1980 (Reel 13, Frame 754)
      - Management Plan, 1986 (Reel 13, Frame 756)
      - Notes on the Future of Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, Mary F. King, 1982 June 1 (Reel 13, Frame 779)
      - Performance Report, 1996-1997 (Reel 13, Frame 792)
      - Performance Report, 1997 June 30 (Reel 13, Frame 820)
      - Performance Report, 1999 December 31 (Reel 13, Frame 858)
      - Performance Report, 2004 December 31 (Reel 13, Frame 905)
      - Performance Report, 2005 March 31 (Reel 13, Frame 1002)
      - Performance Report, 2005 June 30 (Reel 13, Frame 1107)
      - Performance Report, 2005 September 30 (Reel 14, Frame 1)
      - Perspectives on the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, Elizabeth Fair, undated (Reel 14, Frame 227)
      - Process Audit, 1988 (Reel 14, Frame 238)
      - Program Implementation Process, undated (Reel 14, Frame 265)
      - Project Analysis and Evaluation Summary, 1975-1980 (Reel 14, Frame 399)
      - Status Report, 1976 June 22 (Reel 14, Frame 425)
      - Status Report, 1981 September 29 (Reel 14, Frame 564)
      - Status Report, 1996 September 24 (Reel 14, Frame 570)
      - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation Retrospective, 1975-1988 (Reel 14, Frame 692)
    - Thomas McRae, Presidential Files (Reel 14, Frame 700)
      - Policy Development, undated (Reel 14, Frame 701)
      - Thomas McRae, Exit Interview, 1989 March 10 (Reel 14, Frame 708)
    - Historical (Reel 14, Frame 726)
      - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, "The Early Years", undated (Reel 14, Frame 727)
      - Investment Principles, undated (Reel 14, Frame 767)
      - Miscellaneous, 1974-2003 (Reel 14, Frame 771)
      - The 25th Anniversary of the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, 1974-1999 (Reel 14, Frame 805)
      - Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation, 1984-2004 (Reel 14, Frame 820)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller (Reel 14, Frame 843)
      - Winthrop Rockefeller, Biographical Information, 1964 (Reel 14, Frame 844)
      - Governor's Conference on Education, 1967 October 12 (Reel 14, Frame 876)
      - "How Far We Have Come; How Far We Can Go", Winthrop Rockefeller, 1970 June 9 (Reel 14, Frame 886)
      - Interview by John L. Ward, 1972 (Reel 14, Frame 900)
      - Letter to My Son, Winthrop Rockefeller, undated (Reel 14, Frame 860)
      - Programs Begun Under the Administration of Governor Winthrop Rockefeller and Designed to Continue Past, 1971 January 12 1970 December 15 (Reel 14, Frame 1106)
      - The Rockefeller Years, 1967-1970 (Reel 14, Frame 1212)
    - Miscellaneous (Reel 15, Frame 1)
      - Foundation for the Mid South, 2000 (Reel 15, Frame 2)
      - Grants Management Software for Foundations and Corporations, 1996-1997 (Reel 15, Frame 42)
      - Rural Community Jump-Start Technology Initiative, undated (Reel 15, Frame 70)
      - Spending Policies and Investment Planning for Foundations: A Structure for Determining a Foundation's Asset Mix, 1995 (Reel 15, Frame 134)
      - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, Archives and Special Collections, 1983 (Reel 15, Frame 191)
- Grants, 1972-2001; 2 (Reel 15, Frame 203)
  This series is about the grant programs that Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation funded from 1972 to 2001. The organization only funded grants that met two of their criteria: First, the organization had to be in Arkansas and, second, it's activities had to fall within one of the three following areas--economic development, educational opportunities, or racial and social justice.
  - Programs, 1976-2001; 1 (Reel 15, Frame 204)
    Main part of the grant program.
    - Grants, Alpha List, 1999 (Reel 15, Frame 205)
    - Grants, Alpha List, by Fund, 1999 (Reel 15, Frame 255)
    - Grants, Alpha List, by Program Area, 1999 (Reel 15, Frame 288)
    - Organizational Profile Report, 1999 (Reel 15, Frame 357)
    - Closed Grants, 1999 (Reel 15, Frame 587)
    - Grant Declination Reports, 1991-1996 (Reel 15, Frame 595)
    - Photo Album, undated (Reel 15, Frame 676)
    - A Better Chance, Incorporated, 94-201, 1994-2000 (Reel 15, Frame 747)
    - ACES, The Association for Children for Enforcement of Support, Incorporated, 95-164, 1995-1998 (Reel 16, Frame 1)
    - ACES, The Association for Children for Enforcement of Support, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1996 (Reel 16, Frame 318)
    - ACORN Housing Corporation, Incorporated, Affordable Housing, 91-164, 1991 1996 (Reel 16, Frame 322)
    - Acorn School District, 92-59, 1992-1993 (Reel 16, Frame 457)
    - Acorn School District, 94-124, 1994-1995 (Reel 16, Frame 501)
    - Acorn School District, 95-122, 1995 (Reel 16, Frame 538)
    - Advocates and Relatives for Kids, Incorporated, 96-41, 1996-1998 (Reel 16, Frame 574)
    - Advocates for Battered Women, Incorporated, 85-602, 1985-1988 (Reel 16, Frame 645)
    - AETN Foundation, Arkansas Educational Telecommunication Network Foundation, 85-529, 1985-1987 (Reel 16, Frame 666)
    - AETN Foundation, Arkansas Educational Telecommunication Network Foundation, 87-769, 1987-1988 (Reel 16, Frame 695)
    - AETN Foundation, Arkansas Educational Telecommunication Network Foundation, 93-154, 1993-1994 (Reel 16, Frame 720)
    - AETN Foundation, Arkansas Educational Telecommunication Network Foundation, Arkansas/Soviet Union Student Exchange, 1989-1990 (Reel 16, Frame 790)
    - Aid in Community Development, 96-128, 1996-1998 (Reel 16, Frame 796)
    - All Our Children, 94-160, 1994-1995 (Reel 16, Frame 839)
    - Alpena School District, Alpena Elementary School, 91-9, 1991 (Reel 16, Frame 885)
    - Alpena School District, 92-62, 1991-1993 (Reel 16, Frame 919)
    - Alread Community Resource Development Corporation, ACRDC, 91-80, 1991-1992 (Reel 16, Frame 976)
    - Alread Community Resource Development Corporation, ACRDC, 91-111, 1991-1992 (Reel 16, Frame 1034)
    - Alread Community Resource Development Corporation, ACRDC, 92-200, 1992-1997 (Reel 16, Frame 1085)
    - Altheimer-Sherrill Schools, 91-91, 1991-1993 (Reel 16, Frame 1157)
    - American Forum, 92-192, Original Proposal-Year One, 1992-1994 (Reel 17, Frame 1)
    - American Forum, 92-192, Year Two-Year Three, 1993-1995 (Reel 17, Frame 220)
    - American Land Forum, Professional Services Agreement, 1983 (Reel 17, Frame 367)
    - Americans for Civic Participation, 85-530, 1985-1986 (Reel 17, Frame 371)
    - Americans for Civic Participation, 86-691, 1986-1988 (Reel 17, Frame 396)
    - Amity Public Schools, 87-844, 1987-1989 (Reel 17, Frame 434)
    - Amity Public Schools, 88-156, 1988-1989 (Reel 17, Frame 454)
    - Amity Public Schools, 94-8, 1994-1995 (Reel 17, Frame 469)
    - Amity Public Schools, 94-180, 1994-1995 (Reel 17, Frame 530)
    - ACROM, Productions, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1993-1994 (Reel 17, Frame 575)
    - Arch Ford Education Service Cooperative, 92-140, 1992-1994 (Reel 17, Frame 602)
    - Arch Ford Education Service Cooperative, 95-104, 1994-1997 (Reel 17, Frame 768)
    - Argenta Community Development Corporation, 94-158, 1994-1996 (Reel 17, Frame 951)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, 90-28, 1989-1990 (Reel 17, Frame 993)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, Goza Junior High School, 91-21, 1991 (Reel 17, Frame 1055)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, Perritt Primary School, 91-121, 1991-1992 (Reel 17, Frame 1083)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, 92-13, 1991-1992 (Reel 17, Frame 1122)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, Central Primary School, 92-72, 1992-1993 (Reel 17, Frame 1167)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, Goza Junior High School, 92-125, 1992-1993 (Reel 18, Frame 1)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, 92-153, 1992-1993 (Reel 18, Frame 32)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, Central Primary School, 93-32, 1992-1993 (Reel 18, Frame 71)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, 94-64, 1994-1995 (Reel 18, Frame 108)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, 95-15, 1995-1996 (Reel 18, Frame 145)
    - Arkadelphia Public Schools, 95-61, 1995-1996 (Reel 18, Frame 198)
    - Arkansas ABLE, Abilities Based on Long Experience, 85-473, 1985-1986 (Reel 18, Frame 229)
    - Arkansas ABLE, Abilities Based on Long Experience, 85-559, 1986-1987 (Reel 18, Frame 259)
    - Arkansas ABLE, Abilities Based on Long Experience, 88-134, 1988-1989 (Reel 18, Frame 294)
    - Arkansas ABLE, Abilities Based on Long Experience, 89-90, 1989-1990 (Reel 18, Frame 318)
    - Arkansas ABLE, Abilities Based on Long Experience, 91-148, 1991-1993 (Reel 18, Frame 344)
    - Arkansas ABLE, Abilities Based on Long Experience, 95-168, 1995-1998 (Reel 18, Frame 526)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 77-1000, 1977 (Reel 18, Frame 778)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 79-1002, 1979 (Reel 18, Frame 786)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 82-308, 1982 (Reel 18, Frame 795)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 83-341, 1981-1983 (Reel 18, Frame 810)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 83-378, 1983-1984 (Reel 18, Frame 833)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 84-434, 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 861)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 85-499, 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 892)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1985 (Reel 18, Frame 925)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 86-611, 1986-1987 (Reel 18, Frame 933)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, Pre-School Instruction, 87-815, 1987-1988 (Reel 18, Frame 969)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, Arkansas Children's Needs. 87-733, 1987-1988 (Reel 18, Frame 988)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, HIPPY, 88-121, 1988-1989 (Reel 18, Frame 1007)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 88-132, 1988-1989 (Reel 18, Frame 1039)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 89-89, 1989-1990 (Reel 18, Frame 1055)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 91-161, 1991-1993 (Reel 18, Frame 1076)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 94-197, 1994-1995 (Reel 19, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 95-137, 1995-1996 (Reel 19, Frame 104)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 96-163, Original Proposal-Year One, 1995-1997 (Reel 19, Frame 208)
    - Arkansas Advocates for Children and Families, Incorporated, 96-163, Year Two, 1996-1998 (Reel 19, Frame 358)
    - Arkansas Association of Community Development Corporations, Incorporated, 93-231, Original Proposal-Year One, 1993-1996 (Reel 19, Frame 576)
    - Arkansas Association of Community Development Corporations, Incorporated, 93-231, Year Two, 1994-1996 (Reel 19, Frame 759)
    - Arkansas Association of Community Development Corporations, Incorporated, 93-231, Year Three, 1996-1997 (Reel 19, Frame 1011)
    - Arkansas Association of Community Development Corporations, Incorporated, Daphne R. Scott, Professional Services Agreement, 1993-1994 (Reel 20, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Association of Community Development Corporations, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1996-1997 (Reel 20, Frame 44)
    - Arkansas Association of LeadAR Alumni, 90-92, 1991 (Reel 20, Frame 86)
    - Arkansas Association of LeadAR Alumni, 91-152, 1991-1993 (Reel 20, Frame 133)
    - Arkansas Association of LeadAR Alumni, 93-237, 1993-1998 (Reel 20, Frame 172)
    - Arkansas Aviation Historical Society, Incorporated, 90-77, 1989-1996 (Reel 20, Frame 379)
    - Arkansas Aviation Historical Society, Incorporated, Aviation Museum, 90-77, 1990-1996 (Reel 20, Frame 893)
    - Arkansas Aviation Historical Society, Incorporated, 90-127, 1990-1998 (Reel 21, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Baptist College, 96-79, 1996-1997 (Reel 21, Frame 474)
    - Arkansas Baptist State Convention, 93-28, 1993-1994 (Reel 21, Frame 590)
    - Arkansas Broadcasting Foundation, 86-678, 1986-1988 (Reel 21, Frame 654)
    - Arkansas Broadcasting Foundation, 87-793, 1987-1988 (Reel 21, Frame 684)
    - Arkansas Business Development Corporation, Incorporated, 79-1003, 1979 (Reel 21, Frame 700)
    - Arkansas Business Development Corporation, Incorporated, 80-999, 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 714)
    - Arkansas Career Resources, 87-831, 1987-1988 (Reel 21, Frame 725)
    - Arkansas Cattlemen's Association, 94-41, 1994-1995 (Reel 21, Frame 743)
    - Arkansas Chapter of the National Association of Minority Contractors, 87-845, 1987-1988 (Reel 21, Frame 811)
    - Arkansas City Public Schools, Arkansas City High School, 91-125, 1991-1992 (Reel 21, Frame 835)
    - Arkansas Civil Liberties Foundation, Incorporated, 81-229, 1981 (Reel 21, Frame 871)
    - Arkansas Coalition Against Domestic Violence, 80-1000, 1980 (Reel 21, Frame 884)
    - Arkansas Coalition Against Violence to Women and Children, 88-47, 1988-1989 (Reel 21, Frame 897)
    - Arkansas Coalition Against Violence to Women and Children, 90-134, 1991 (Reel 21, Frame 949)
    - Arkansas Coalition Against Violence to Women and Children, 91-160, 1991-1992 (Reel 21, Frame 1064)
    - Arkansas Coalition for the Handicapped, 82-303, 1982 (Reel 21, Frame 1141)
    - Arkansas Coalition for the Handicapped, 83-360, 1983-1984 (Reel 21, Frame 1157)
    - Arkansas Coalition for the Handicapped, 84-429, 1984-1985 (Reel 22, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Coalition for the Handicapped, 85-600, 1985-1987 (Reel 22, Frame 31)
    - Arkansas Coalition for the Handicapped, 88-52, 1988-1990 (Reel 22, Frame 61)
    - Arkansas College, Institute of Politics and Government, 78-1002, 1978 (Reel 22, Frame 97)
    - Arkansas College, Institute of Politics and Government, Arkansas Constitutional Convention, 78-1009, 1978 (Reel 22, Frame 106)
    - Arkansas College, Original Proposal-Grant Agreements, 1990-1992 (Reel 22, Frame 123)
      Grant number: 90-104
    - Arkansas College, 90-104, Year One-Year Three, 1989-1993 (Reel 22, Frame 262)
    - Arkansas College, Break the Mold, 92-173, 1992-1994 (Reel 22, Frame 479)
    - Arkansas College, Small Business Center, 93-78, 1993-1997 (Reel 22, Frame 510)
    - Arkansas Community Education Development Association, 80-175, 1980-1982 (Reel 22, Frame 736)
    - Arkansas Community Education Development Association, School Based Development Enterprises, 81-252, 1982 (Reel 22, Frame 754)
    - Arkansas Community Education Development Association, Community Education Center on Aging, 82-292, 1982 (Reel 22, Frame 768)
    - Arkansas Community Education Development Association, School Based Development Enterprises, 82-315, 1983 (Reel 22, Frame 786)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 76-888-80-888, 1976-1980 (Reel 22, Frame 800)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, Business Investment and Awards Program, 81-230, 1981 (Reel 22, Frame 842)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 1981 (Reel 22, Frame 852)
      Challenge Grant, 81-231
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 82-305, 1982-1983 (Reel 22, Frame 865)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, Arkansas for the Arts, 82-283, 1982-1983 (Reel 22, Frame 880)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 83-370, 1983-1984 (Reel 22, Frame 894)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 83-381, 1983-1984 (Reel 22, Frame 920)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 85-508, 1985-1986 (Reel 22, Frame 949)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 86-587, 1986 (Reel 22, Frame 977)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 86-624, 1986-1987 (Reel 22, Frame 1004)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 86-710, 1986-1988 (Reel 22, Frame 1031)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 1987-1988 (Reel 22, Frame 1046)
      Challenge Grant, 87-779/87-820/87-824
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, Election Laws, 87-834, 1987-1989 (Reel 22, Frame 1063)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, Cornerstone Project, 88-28, 1988-1990 (Reel 22, Frame 1085)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 88-60, 1988-1989 (Reel 22, Frame 1135)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 88-133, 1988-1989 (Reel 22, Frame 1152)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 88-135, 1988-1991 (Reel 22, Frame 1173)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 89-122, 1989-1991 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 90-80, 1990-1991 (Reel 23, Frame 36)
    - Arkansas Community Foundation, Incorporated, 94-137, 1994-1995 (Reel 23, Frame 95)
    - Arkansas Conference Churches, 86-609, 1986-1988 (Reel 23, Frame 132)
    - Arkansas Consumer Research, 78-1003-79-1003, 1978-1979 (Reel 23, Frame 162)
    - Arkansas Consumer Research, Five Year Planning Retreat, 79-1004, 1979 (Reel 23, Frame 176)
    - Arkansas Consumer Research, 79-1005, 1979 (Reel 23, Frame 185)
    - Arkansas Consumer Research, 79-1024, 1979 (Reel 23, Frame 196)
    - Arkansas Delta Foundation, Incorporated, 92-42, 1991-1993 (Reel 23, Frame 205)
    - Arkansas Delta Foundation, Incorporated, Ventures in Education, 92-81, 1989-1996 (Reel 23, Frame 341)
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, 81-244, 1981-1982 (Reel 23, Frame 640)
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, 83-331, 1983-1984 (Reel 23, Frame 657)
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, 84-404, 1984-1985 (Reel 23, Frame 691)
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, 85-485, 1985-1986 (Reel 23, Frame 724)
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, Affordable Housing, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1991-1993 (Reel 23, Frame 751)
      Grant number: 91-165
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, Affordable Housing, 91-165, Year One-Year Three, 1991-1996 (Reel 23, Frame 891)
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, 94-189, 1994-1998 (Reel 24, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Delta Housing Development Corporation, Incorporated, 96-39, 1994-1998 (Reel 24, Frame 230)
    - Arkansas Delta Law Foundation, 90-65, 1990-1992 (Reel 24, Frame 464)
    - Arkansas Department of Computer Services, Professional Service Agreement, 1993 (Reel 24, Frame 506)
    - Arkansas Department of Correction, Needs Assessment, 79-1009, 1979-1980 (Reel 24, Frame 518)
    - Arkansas Department of Correction, Training Academy, 80-1004, 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 527)
    - Arkansas Department of Education, Program for Effective Teaching, 79-2000, 1979-1981 (Reel 24, Frame 541)
    - Arkansas Department of Education, 83-376, 1983-1984 (Reel 24, Frame 575)
    - Arkansas Department of Education, 85-525, 1985-1988 (Reel 24, Frame 595)
    - Arkansas Department of Education, 86-578, 1986-1987 (Reel 24, Frame 617)
    - Arkansas Department of Education, 87-759, 1987-1988 (Reel 24, Frame 647)
    - Arkansas Department of Education, Middle Grade, 90-98, 1990-1992 (Reel 24, Frame 665)
    - Arkansas Department of Education, 93-40, 1993-1995 (Reel 24, Frame 814)
    - Arkansas Department of Health, Rural Primary Care Conference, 79-1015, 1979-1980 (Reel 24, Frame 891)
    - Arkansas Department of Health, Venereal Disease Task Force, 80-0030, 1980 (Reel 24, Frame 900)
    - Arkansas Department of Health, 1992-1993 (Reel 24, Frame 913)
      Planning Grant, 92-138
    - Arkansas Department of Higher Education, 83-386, 1983-1984 (Reel 24, Frame 975)
    - Arkansas Department of Higher Education, 84-432, 1984-1986 (Reel 24, Frame 1000)
    - Arkansas Department of Higher Education, 89-119, 1989-1991 (Reel 24, Frame 1029)
    - Arkansas Department of Higher Education, Dean's Leadership Forum, 92-141, 1992-1994 (Reel 25, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Department of Human Services, 87-855, 1987-1989 (Reel 25, Frame 243)
    - Arkansas Department of Local Services, Division of Community Services, Day Care in Family Homes, 78-1014, 1978 (Reel 25, Frame 260)
    - Arkansas Department of Natural and Cultural Heritage, The Nature Conservancy, 78-1015, 1978-1979 (Reel 25, Frame 275)
    - Arkansas Development and Finance Authority, 95-80, 1995-1999 (Reel 25, Frame 313)
    - Arkansas Disability Coalition, 90-96, 1990-1991 (Reel 25, Frame 548)
    - Arkansas Disability Coalition, 91-151, 1991-1993 (Reel 25, Frame 604)
    - Arkansas Disability Coalition, 91-159, Original Proposal, 1991-1996 (Reel 25, Frame 649)
    - Arkansas Disability Coalition, Grant Agreement-Year Two, 1991-1996 (Reel 25, Frame 941)
      Grant number: 91-159
    - Arkansas Disability Coalition, 91-159, Year Three-Year Five, 1993-1997 (Reel 26, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Economic Corporation, 93-221, 1993-1994 (Reel 26, Frame 194)
    - Arkansas Economic Corporation, Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1994-1996 (Reel 26, Frame 253)
      Grant number: 94-194
    - Arkansas Economic Corporation, 94-194, Year One-Year Three, 1993-1997 (Reel 26, Frame 392)
    - Arkansas Education Renewal Consortium, Incorporated, 88-155, 1990-1993 (Reel 26, Frame 609)
    - Arkansas Education Renewal Consortium, Incorporated, 91-146, Original Proposal-Year Two, 1991-1996 (Reel 26, Frame 637)
    - Arkansas Education Renewal Consortium, Incorporated, 91-146, Year Three-Year Four, 1993-1996 (Reel 26, Frame 896)
    - Arkansas Endowment for the Humanities, Multi-State Workshop on Family Farmer, 79-1017, 1979 (Reel 26, Frame 1133)
    - Arkansas Endowment for the Humanities, 85-532, 1985-1986 (Reel 26, Frame 1198)
    - Arkansas Endowment for the Humanities. 87-821, 1987-1988 (Reel 27, Frame 1)
    - Arkansas Endowment for the Humanities, 88-27, 1988-1992 (Reel 27, Frame 21)
    - Arkansas Enterprise Group, 88-166, 1988-1991 (Reel 27, Frame 60)
    - Arkansas Extension Homemakers Council, 92-136, 1992-1993 (Reel 27, Frame 123)
    - Arkansas Extension Homemakers Council, 94-154, 1994-1995 (Reel 27, Frame 175)
    - Arkansas Extension Homemakers Council, 95-29, 1995 (Reel 27, Frame 217)